うお～っ！
ふん！
うわっ…。
The small fry can stay out of this!
ザコは 引っ込んでな！
さあ かかってきな カカシ。
All right! Come at me, Kakashi!
Breaking the Crystal Style
(トビ)頭隠して 尻隠さず。
Hide my face, but not my butt!
(トビ)あん？
Oh?
先輩に思いを寄せる女子高生。
I'm a schoolgirl in love
with her Senpai!
あ あら？ ちょっと先輩！
O-Oh? Hey Senpai!
Are you still angry?
まだ怒ってるんですか？
仲よく 一緒に
三尾探しましょうよ！
Let's be friends and
look for Three-Tail's together.
(デイダラ)失せろ！
Get lost!
だって 仕事しないと➡
But if we don't get to work,
the others will chew us out.
他の先輩に
また怒られちゃいますよ！
もう 許してくださいよ～。
Please give me a break.
あっ そうだ！ 仮面の中
特別に見せちゃいます。
I know! I'll let you take
a special peek inside the mask.
失せろと言ってるんだ！
I said get lost!
もう先輩！
そんなこと言うと➡
Oh Senpai! I just might go somewhere
for real if you say it like that!
ホント どっか行っちゃいますよ！
ああ もう しようがないな。
I have no choice...
しばらくは １人で探すか。
I'll go search by myself for a while.
そりゃっ！
So this is the power
she kept hidden...
《これが ヤツが秘めていた力か》
あきらめの悪い…。
So persistent...
墨絵が効かないと
後は逃げるだけ。
And when your ink drawing
doesn't work, you run away...
それが お前の忍法か。
Is that your Ninja Art?
ボクの墨の使い方は
それだけじゃない。
There are other uses for my ink.
なに…。
What...?
うおぉ！
忍法 墨流し。
Ninja Art: Ink Flush.
さぁ どうした？
かかってきなよ！
What's the matter?
Come at me!
《まいったね…
コイツ前に戦ったときは➡
I'm fed up...
When we last fought,
she didn't release all her power?
まだ すべての力を
出していなかったのか》
チッ！ 次は 本気を出すよ！
The next one's for real!
晶遁！ 破晶降龍！
Crystal Style:
Burst Crystal Falling Dragon!
なに!?
死にな！
Wha--?!
Die!
《コイツは 接触する
あらゆる物質を結晶化させる。
She can turn anything
she touches into crystal.
つまり 水遁 土遁 木遁は
効果がない。
In other words, Water, Earth
nor Wood Styles have any effect.
しかし これなら！》
However...this will...!
やったか!?
Did I do it...?
甘いね！
So naïve...
ぐおっ!!
残念だったね カカシ。
Too bad, Kakashi.
三匹の龍は オレを
移動させないための目くらましか。
The three-tailed dragon was
just a diversion to keep me here...
なんだかんだ言っても➡
For all the talk I've heard,
your Sharingan isn't much.
大したことないね
写輪眼のカカシも。
もう遊びは終わりだよ。
Well now, playtime is over.
ムダだ。
うが～っ！
It's useless.
(トビ)さ～て
どこかな？ どこかな？
Now then, where is it, where is it?
っていうか どこに行くかな…。
Actually, where should I go...
ん？
Huh?
なんか むちゃくちゃ
怪しい湖 発見。
I've discovered an awfully suspicious lake!
Hmm?
何やってんだ？ アイツら。
What're they doing anyway?
あれは 木ノ葉の…。
They're from the Hidden Leaf...
キャッ！
H-Hey!
ちょっと！
いの！
Ino... focus on the Chakra
for the barrier!
結界を張るチャクラに集中して！
は… はい！
R-Right!
結界？ ヘッ！ まさか。
いや まさか まさか。
Barrier? Hey no way...
That's impossible.
ん？ あらら…
もう一匹いるけど➡
Huh?
Oh my... There's another one...
見たことねえな…。
But I've never seen him before.
《麟児 : 木ノ葉の連中
三尾を見つけだすつもりか？》
The Hidden Leaf...
are looking for Three-Tails?
ハッ！ まぁ 高見の見物といくか。
Oh well...
I guess I'll just sit back and watch.
さ～て…
そろそろ 決着をつけるよ！
Okay, let's settle this!
カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei...!
覚悟しな！
Prepare to die...!
なにっ!?
What?!
シノ！
Oh! Shino!
間一髪ってところだね。
できたのか？
Just in the nick of time.
Are they ready?
できていなければ
ここには来ない。
If they weren't, I wouldn't have come.
ふぅ… 誰かと思えば 蟲使いかい。
Humph... If it isn't the Insect user.
お前の術じゃ
私に通用しないよ！
Your Jutsu is useless against me.
ムダなんだよ！
It's useless!
だから 言っただろう？ ムダだって。
Didn't I tell you? It's useless.
それはどうかな。
I wonder about that...
What?!
なに!?
バカな…！
It can't be!
お前の術は
もう オレには効かない。
Your Jutsu won't work against me.
なぜなら オレの蟲は
無限の進化を遂げる。
And that's because
my insects can evolve limitlessly.
お前の術への耐性は得た。
They are now resistant to your Jutsu.
よし やった！ すげぇぞ！
Yes, you did it! That's amazing!
ありえない…
私の晶遁が やぶれるなんて…。
That's impossible...
My Crystal Style can't be defeated...
多重影分身の術！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
もう 逃がしゃしねぇってばよ！
I won't let you get away now!
Stay still!
(カカシ)おとなしくしろ。
幽鬼丸は どこにいる!?
Where is Yuukimaru?!
なんで お前…。 あ！
Why do you...?!
お前だって
あの子の力が欲しいんだろ？
You want that boy's power too?
オレは そんなもんいらねえ！
どうだかな。
I don't need anything like that!
I wonder about that...
あぁっ！
(シノ)今だ！
ヤツの晶遁は封じられた。
Now...! Her Crystal Style
has been sealed!
Tell us!
白状しやがれ！
幽鬼丸は どこだ!?
Where is Yuukimaru?!
この！
Why you--!
これは！
This is...!
紅蓮さん…。
Guren...
これは… 泥!?
This is...mud?
どうやら あの結晶は
すぐ修復するようだ。
It seems that Crystal
mends itself right away.
Damn it! There's no end to this!
クソ！ やっても やっても
きりがねえ！
Focus the Insects' attack on one spot.
蟲の攻撃を一点に集中させろ！
紅蓮さん…。
Guren...
《間に合わない！》
I can't keep up...!
Lightning Blade!
雷切！
泥の壁!?
A mud wall?!
牛頭!?
Gozu?!
牛頭… お前！
Gozu, you...
何しやがる!? 放せ！
What're you doing?!
Let go! I'm going to kill them...!
私は ヤツらにとどめを…。
牛頭…。
Gozu...?
ここは通さない！
I won't let you through!
うぅ…。
紅蓮さん！
Guren!
Are you all right, Kakashi Sensei?!
大丈夫か!? カカシ先生！
あぁ。
Yeah... But...
だが 紅蓮には逃げられた。
くっ！
Guren got away.
幽鬼丸の居場所をつきとめる
手がかりだったのに。
She was the key to finding Yuukimaru...!
残念だ。 なぜなら➡
It's regrettable...
My insects performed flawlessly,
yet she got away...
オレの蟲は 完璧に働いたのに➡
逃げられたからだ。
いいか？ 手分けして探す。
All right, we'll split up and search!
ナルトはシノと。 サイはオレについて来い。
Naruto, you go with Shino.
Sai, come with me!
みなさんが
すごいヤツらだって煽るから➡
You said that they were formidable,
闘志を燃やしていたんですが…。
so I was burning with the desire to fight...
What was that?
They were so easy to beat.
何あれ？ 全然じゃない。
ああ。
この間と別人みたいだったぜ。
Yup... They were so different
from the last time.
Are you real sure about these
next guys?
他のヤツらも
前評判だけじゃないの？
油断しないように。
はい。
Don't let your guard down.
Y-Yes!
カカシ先輩が苦戦したくらいだ。
Kakashi Senpai had
his hands full with her.
晶遁使いは本物だよ。
The Crystal Style user is no joke!
ボクの体術が通じるか
ぜひ 手合わせしたいものです。
I'd love to face her in battle...
to see if my Taijutsu is effective
against her!
ここで二手に別れよう。
Let's split up into two groups here.
Lee and Tenten will guard
the Sealing team by the lake!
リーとテンテンは
湖面の封印班の警護を。
我々は 先輩の対晶遁班と➡
And we will join up with Senpai's team
who are battling the Crystal Style user!
合流する。
はい。
Right!
ええ！
晶遁使いと戦えないんですか？
Huh? I won't be able to fight
the Crystal Style user?
敵は どこに現れるか わからない。
We don't know where
the enemy may appear.
油断するなと言ったはずだよ。
I just told you not to
let your guard down...!
(リー/テンテン)は はい！
- Y-Yes!
- Yes!
SEARCH
あっ 今…。
Huh?! Just now...!
わかってる。 この近く…。
I know... It's close...
この真下にいる。
Directly below us...
いよいよね。
It's finally come...
(シズネ)結界四方封陣を
「探」のモードから切り替える。
We are switching from the "search" mode
of the Four-Corner Sealing Barrier.
息を乱さないで。 いくわよ。
Keep your breathing soft and steady.
Here we go!
- Four-Corner Sealing Barrier: Bind!
(みんな)結界四方封陣 「縛」！
BIND
このまま 網を静かに沈めていく。
We'll quietly sink the net.
Do not let the Three-Tails detect us!
三尾に気配を気取られるな。
ちょっと先輩 やっぱ三尾ですよ！
って いないんですよ。
Oh no, Senpai!
It is the Three Tails, after all...!
Right, he's not here...
ん？
Huh?!
(トビ)アイツ 止めるつもりか？
Does he intend to stop them?
敵が！
(サクラたち)えっ!?
The enemy...!
(シズネ)気を乱すな。
(いの)でも…。
Concentrate!
But!
Leaf Hurricane!
木ノ葉旋風！
What?!
なに!?
リーさん。 テンテンさん。
Lee! Tenten!
We've taken care of
the enemy on that side,
向こうの敵が終わったんで
急いで駆けつけてきました。
so we rushed over.
間に合ってよかったです。
I'm glad we made it in time!
ボクが来たからには この４人に
指一本 触れさせません。
Now that I'm here,
I won't allow you to lay
a finger on these four!
お前たちは
足止めしてあったはずだ。
There should've been others to stop you...
ああ 彼らですか？
Oh, them...
They were no match for us.
ボクたちの敵じゃありませんね。
Damn... So Kigiri and
the others were beaten...
く… 鬼霧たちが敗れたのか。
さぁ ボクが相手します。
Now then, I am your opponent!
チッ…。
What? Running away?!
(テンテン)なによ 逃げるの!?
Uh-oh... This is bad. Real bad!
(トビ)あらららら やばい やばいよ。
At this rate,
the Three-Tails will be sealed!
このままじゃ
三尾封印されちゃうじゃん。
But if I go out now, I might lose.
I'm outnumbered.
でも 今出てっても
やられちゃうかな？
向こう人数多いし… ねぇ 先輩？
Right, Senpai? And he's not here...
…って いない。
《カブト : フン… どいつも こいつも
使えないヤツばかりだな。
Humph...
Useless, the whole lot of them.
木ノ葉の術式は 三尾の封印。
The Hidden Leaf ritual aims
to seal the Three-Tails.
三尾を誰にも利用されない道を
選んだのか…。
They've chosen a path
which will prevent anyone
from using the Three-Tails.
But I won't allow that.
そうは させられない》
(カブト)幽鬼丸？
Yuukimaru...?
紅蓮さん…。
Guren...
《イヤだ… 白い椿は
赤い椿になっちゃダメなんだ…。
No... The white camellia
cannot become a red one.
約束だよ… 帰ってきて》
You promised...that you'll come back!
ゴ… 牛頭… お前…。
Gozu... You...
♪♪(草笛)
((幽鬼丸？
Yuukimaru...?
(はっ!? キャア!!))
♪♪(草笛)
No! This grass whistle...
こ… この草笛は…。
まさか… まさか… まさか…。
No way...
No way... It's impossible...
あっ…。
♪♪(草笛)
うわぁ～!!
《私が… あの子の母親を
殺したというのか!?
Did I kill that boy's mother...?!
そんな… そんな!?》
That's... That's...!
(カブト)紅蓮。
あっ!?
Guren...
行くぞ。
お前 大蛇丸様のところに➡
We must go.
You?! I thought you returned
to Lord Orochimaru.
帰ったんじゃないのか!?
それどころじゃなくなった。
There's something more pressing.
The Hidden Leaf has started
to seal the Three-Tails.
木ノ葉の封印術に
三尾が かかってしまってね。
What?
なんだと!?
幽鬼丸を使って三尾を操る。
We'll use Yuukimaru to
control the Three-Tails.
そして ヤツらの結界を破るんだ。
And we'll destroy their barrier.
Kabuto, I need to talk to you.
カブト 話がある。
なんだ この時間のないときに…。
What, at a time like this?
I know that.
わかってる。
だが これ以上 力を使わせれば➡
But you of all people should know
what would happen
if we make Yuukimaru use
his powers any further...
幽鬼丸が どうなるか
アンタなら わかるはずだ！
Huh? Is that all?
なんだ そんなことか…。
本当のことを話せ！
Tell me the truth!
Why're you so upset?
(カブト)何を カッカしてる。
It's none of your business
whether Yuukimaru lives or dies.
幽鬼丸が生きようと生きまいと
お前には 関係があるまい。
It is...my business.
関係は… ある。
Oh? So even the devil sheds tears?
ほぉ～ 鬼の目にも涙
というわけか。
これまで数え切れないほど
人を殺してきたお前が➡
To think that you,
who have killed countless people,
幽鬼丸に情を寄せるとはね。
would have a soft spot for Yuukimaru.
Now that is a surprise.
これは驚きだ。
(紅蓮)あの子は特別だ！
He's special...
あの子の母親を殺したからか？
どうして それを？
Because you killed his mother?
How did you...?
別に不思議じゃない。
There's nothing unusual about that.
大蛇丸様は すべて お見通しだ。
It's as Lord Orochimaru predicted.
お前があの子に転ぶってこともね。
He knew that you would
have feelings for the boy.
だからこそ お前を選んだ。
That's exactly why he chose you.
なんなら ボクから幽鬼丸に
教えてあげてもいいんだけどね。
If you like,
I can tell Yuukimaru for you...
唯一 帰る場所だと信じていた
優しい紅蓮さんは➡
That the kind, gentle Guren
whom he believes
is the one he should return to...
自分の母親を殺した
極悪人だったってね。
is the evil villain who killed his mother...
Stop!
やめろ！
Then, carry out my orders.
なら ボクの命令に
素直に従うんだね。
Tenten...
テンテン いつまた
敵が来るか わかりません。
We don't know when
the enemy will appear again.
油断しないでください。
Please stay alert.
よく なつかせたものだ。
You endeared him to you very skillfully...
ウフフ ウフフ…！
《カブト : 大蛇丸様 悔しいが➡
Lord Orochimaru...
I hate to admit it,
but you were right to select that woman...
あの女を選んだのは
間違っていませんでしたよ》
Guren will grow to love Yuukimaru?
Is that even possible?
((カブト : 紅蓮が
幽鬼丸に情を寄せる？
そんなことがあるのですか？
(大蛇丸)フッ… カブト
お前も まだまだね。
Kabuto, you have much to learn.
同じ時をすごせば すごすほど
絆は深くなる。
人間とは そういうものよ。
そうでしょうか。
(大蛇丸)あの２人は
深い因縁で結ばれている。
おそらく 紅蓮は
私の命令を忘れて裏切るわ。
(そのときは…))
《カブト : そろそろ 頃合いですかね
大蛇丸様…》